A Guide to the Fritz Albert Lipmann papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA123
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional Societies, 1957-1979; 6; 6 Cubic Feet
  - American Chemical Society, 1970-1971 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - American Chemical Society, 1973-1974 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - American Chemical Society national meeting, 1959 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - American Chemical Society national meeting, 1964 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - American Chemical Society symposium on microstructure of proteins (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - American Institute of Biological Sciences (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - American Longevity Association (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - American Society for Microbiology (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - American Society for Microbiology - New York meeting, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - American Society for Microbiology, 1986 March 20-23 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 1 of 2 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 2 of 2 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists-Council material (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1957-1959 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 1 of 4 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 2 of 4 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 3 of 4 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 4 of 4 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1961; 1 of 4 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1961; 2 of 4 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1961; 3 of 4 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1961; 4 of 4 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1962-1964 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1965-1966 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1967-1970 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1970-1973 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - American Society of Biological Chemist, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists-annual meeting, 1961 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists-genetics symposium (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Arden House (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Carlsberg Foundation (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - CIBA-cell regulation (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Symposium (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum vitae and press releases, 1 of 3 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum vitae and press releases, 2 of 3 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Curriculum vitae and press releases, 3 of 3 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - EMBO, 1 of 5 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - EMBO, 2 of 5 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - EMBO, 3 of 5 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - EMBO, 4 of 5 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - EMBO, 5 of 5 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - EMBO-2, 1 of 2 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - EMBO-2, 2 of 2 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - EMBO forms and instructions (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - EMBO, 1969-1970 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - EMBO, 1971; 1 of 3 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - EMBO, 1971; 2 of 3 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - EMBO, 1971; 3 of 3 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - EMBO, 1972; 1 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - EMBO, 1972; 2 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - EMBO, 1973; 1 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - EMBO, 1973; 2 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Faber Foundation (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - FEBS (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Federation of American Scientists (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Federation meetings-Lipmann dinner (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Federation meetings, 1959-1963 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Federation meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Federation meetings, 1968 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Federation meetings, 1969 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Federation meetings, 1970 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Federation meetings, 1973 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Federation meetings, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Federation meetings, 1975 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Federation meetings, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Federation meetings, 1977 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Federation meetings, 1978 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Federation meetings, 1979 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Federation meetings, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Federation meetings, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Federation meetings, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Federation meetings, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Federation meetings, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Fifth International Biochemical Congress, Moscow, 1961; 1 of 2 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Fifth International Biochemical Congress, Moscow, 1961; 2 of 2 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Funaguma. Dr. Tooru (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Gordon conferences (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Grants-transfer requests (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Honoraria requests (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Institut de la Vie, Versailles, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Institut de la Vie, Vienna, 1979 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Institut de la Vie, Vienna, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Insurance claims (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Insurance policies (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - International Congress for Microbiology (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Labaratory animal center, 1 of 2 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Labaratory animal center, 2 of 2 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Lee, Dr. Sung (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Life sciences (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Lipmann reunion dinner, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - McClean Hospital Scientific Advisory Committee, 1 of 2 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - McClean Hospital Scientific Advisory Committee, 2 of 2 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Medicare (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital Scientific Advisory Committee, 1 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital Scientific Advisory Committee, 2 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital Scientific Advisory Committee, 3 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital Scientific Advisory Committee, 4 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 2 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 3 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 4 of 4 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1 of 5 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 2 of 5 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 3 of 5 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 4 of 5 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 5 of 5 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences Fall meeting (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences refereed papers, 1 of 2 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences refereed papers, 2 of 2 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1957-1958 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1959 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1960; 1 of 2 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1960; 2 of 2 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1961 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1962 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1963 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1964; 1 of 3 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1964; 2 of 3 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1964; 3 of 3 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1965; 1 of 2 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1965; 2 of 2 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1966; 1 of 2 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1966; 2 of 2 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1967 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1968; 1 of 2 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1968; 2 of 2 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1969 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1970 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1971; 1 of 2 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1971; 2 of 2 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1972 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences refereed papers, 1 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences refereed papers, 2 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences refereed papers, 3 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1975; 1 of 2 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1975; 2 of 2 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1976; 1 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1976; 2 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1976; 3 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1977; 1 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1977; 2 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1977; 3 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1977; 4 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1978; 1 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1978; 2 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1978; 3 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1978; 4 of 4 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - National Council for Civic Responsibility (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - National Heart Institute, 1 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - National Heart Institute, 2 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - National Institute of Health grant (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - National Institute of Health application (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - National Institute of Health grants, 1957-1958 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - National Institute of Health grant number 13972-16 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - National Institute of Health grant number 13972-17 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - National Institute of Health grant number 13972-18 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - National Institute of Health grant number 13972-19 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - National Institute of Health grant number 13972-20 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - National Institute of Health grant number 13972-21 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - National Institute of Health grant information (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - National Institute of Health Gregory grant (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation Continuation grant (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation grant application, 1 of 2 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation grant application, 2 of 2 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation grants (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation Interdisciplinary Enzyme Group (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation grants, 1957-1962 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation meeting, 1957 October 25-26 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation meeting expenses (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation, 1958-1960; 1 of 3 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation, 1958-1960; 2 of 3 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation, 1958-1960; 3 of 3 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation, 1961 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, 1962 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation, 1964 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation, 1965; 1 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation, 1965; 2 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation, 1966 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation, 1967; 1 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation, 1967; 2 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation, 1967; 3 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation, 1968; 1 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation, 1968; 2 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation, 1968; 3 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969-1970; 1 of 3 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969-1970; 2 of 3 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969-1970; 3 of 3 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971; 1 of 2 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation, 1971; 2 of 2 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation, 1973 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation, 1974; 1 of 3 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation, 1974; 2 of 3 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - National Science Foundation, 1974; 3 of 3 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation, 1982-1986; 1 of 2 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation, 1982-1986; 2 of 2 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1968 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Philosophical Society (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Pontifical Academy of Sciences meeting Rome, 1 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Pontifical Academy of Sciences meeting Rome, 2 of 2 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Royal Society London (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Royal Society anniversary meeting, 1963 November (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller University Press (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Shouldice Hospital (hernia operation) (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Sixth International Congress of Biochemistry, 1 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Sixth International Congress of Biochemistry, 2 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Sixth International Congress of Biochemistry, 3 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Symposium on enzyme chemistry (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Vienna Congress, 1958 September (Box 148, Folder 14)
- Nobel Prize Files, 1953; 7; 0.33 Cubic Feet
  Includes biographical material, congratulations correspondence, newspaper clippings, photographs, press releases.
  Arranged by subject.
  - Nobel Prize biography (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - [Nobel Prize booklets] (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Nobel Prize Ceremony Photographs, 1 of 2 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Nobel Prize Ceremony Photographs, 2 of 2 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Nobel Prize clippings (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Nobel Prize correspondence (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - [Nobel Prize miscellaneous] (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Nobel Prize press releases (Box 149, Folder 8)
- Photographs, 1930-1986; 8; 0.33 Cubic Feet
  Includes photographs spanning Dr Lipmann's entire career, from 1930 in Germany up to a few months before his death. Subjects include awards ceremonies, colleagues, formal portraits, informal shots, laboratory groups, lectures, parties, vacations.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by subject; many photos not dated or identified.
  - 1963 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Madrid, 1969 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - [meeting], 1970s (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Awards ceremonies (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Bethesda meeting, Spring 1982 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Brandeis Graduation, 1959 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Brandeis University symposium, 1982 June (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Campus views (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Christmas party, 1978 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Colleagues (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Colleagues, 1970 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Colleagues group shots (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Copenhagen laboratory, 1930s-1940s (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - FASEB meeting (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - Gene expression work session, 1966 November 20-22 (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - Informal shots (Box 150, Folder 16)
  - Israel meeting (Box 150, Folder 17)
  - Kyoto, Japan (Box 150, Folder 18)
  - Laboratory and others (Box 150, Folder 19)
  - Lindau conference (Box 150, Folder 20)
  - Lipmann Eighty-second birthday party (Box 150, Folder 21)
  - Lipmann Eighty-fifth birthday party Japan (Box 150, Folder 22)
  - Lipmann laboratory (Box 150, Folder 23)
  - Lipmann picnic (Box 150, Folder 24)
  - Luncheon in Squibb Park, 1954 June 8 (Box 150, Folder 25)
  - [meeting], circa late 1950s-early 1960s (Box 150, Folder 26)
  - New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1953 September 18 (Box 150, Folder 27)
  - New Hampton Schoo, 1958 June 16-20 (Box 150, Folder 28)
  - Paris meeting (Box 150, Folder 29)
  - Portraits (Box 150, Folder 30)
  - Protein metabolism symposium, 1968 April (Box 150, Folder 31)
  - Rockefeller University graduation, 1964-1965 (Box 150, Folder 32)
  - Sixth International Biochemistry Congress, 1964 (Box 150, Folder 33)
  - Strasbourg, 1981 September 23 (Box 150, Folder 34)
  - Symposium 1969 Cold Spring Harbor (Box 150, Folder 35)
  - Symposium on protein synthesis (Box 150, Folder 36)
  - Vatican meetings, 1961 (Box 150, Folder 37)
  - Photographs (Box 171)
- Rolodex Files, 1950s; 9; 0.33 Cubic Feet
  Includes one file with names and addresses of colleagues. Second file contains list of colleagues to be sent reprints.
  Rolodex file cards, 3 x 5, containing hundreds of addresses.
  Arrangement
  - Rolodex Files, 1950s (Box 151)
- Slides, undated (probably 1960s); 10; 2 Cubic Feet
  Slides consist of scientific drawings, graphs and microscopic photographs. Probably used in conjunction with lectures and publications.
  Hundreds of slides of scientific photographs, drawings and graphs none identified.
  Arranged as found; none are identified or dated.
  - Slides, undated: probably 1960s (Box 153, Box 155, Box 154, Box 156, Box 157, Box 152)
- Negatives, 1950s; 11; 1 Cubic Feet
  Arranged as found; many not identified or dated.
  Negatives of drawings, graphs and microscopic photographs used in articles and slides.
  Hundreds of negatives used to make slides and reproduce scientific illustrations none identified.
  - Negatives, 1950s; 11 (Box 158, Box 159, Box 160)
- Lipmann Reprints, 1924-1985; 12; 2.5 Cubic Feet
  Includes at least one copy (with a few exceptions) of every article Dr. Lipmann published. Two copies are included for the majority of articles, although with earlier articles only one copy could be found.
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - Lipmann reprints 1-90, two bound volumes (Box 161)
  - Lipmann reprints 91-166, two bound volumes (Box 162)
  - Lipmann reprints 167-272, two bound volumes (Box 163)
  - Lipmann reprints 273-330, two bound volumes (Box 164)
  - Lipmann reprints 331-399, one bound volume (Box 165)
  - Lipmann reprints 400-449, one bound volume (Box 166)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 13, 17, 49, 51, 64, 123, 141, 149, 153, 173, 174, 175, 176, 183, 185, 206, 207 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 227, 227a,230, 232, 236, 237, 241, 243a, 249, 255, 258, 262, 263, 265 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 267, 270, 271, 273, 282, 283, 293, 298, 299 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 301, 302, 305, 311-313, 316, 317, 320-322, 328, 345, 355, 364, 367a, 370, 374, 375 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 382 (e & f), 388, 408-412, 413, 414-415 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 386. 394, 397, 416-420, 421b, 422-425 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 427-431, 433-434, 435 (b & c), 436 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 437-446, 448 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 449-457, 459-465 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 466-479 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 480-483, 485-493 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - unbound single copy article reprints - 494-516 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Bibliography of Reprints (Box 168, Folder 8)
- Audio-visual Material, various; 1960; 13; 0.75 Cubic Feet
  Various audio-visual material: audio reels, cassettes and film reels. Audio cassettes contain recordings of Dr Lipmann giving lectures in San Francisco and Harvard. Other media not identified.
  - audio cassettes (Box 169)
    Conditions Governing Access
    RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media, due to the specialized equipment necessary to facilitate playback. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
    - unidentified
      RAC is unable to provide access to the original item, due to the specialized equipment necessary to facilitate playback. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
    - San Francisco lecture 4 Part one, 1972 January 27
    - San Francisco lecture 4 Part two, 1972 January 27
    - San Francisco lecture 5, 1972 February 3
    - First lecture, 1972 January 6
    - Second lecture, 1972 January 13
    - Third lecture, 1972 January 20
    - Biochemistry lecture, 1972 March 2
  - microfilm (Box 169)
    - reels: Cambridge University Library, PAD 4671, A. Sarabhai, 176 exposures Negative of Sarabhai thesis, 1969 April 3
    - canister: Chantrenne notebook microfilm, 1950
  - audio reels (Box 169)
    - Israel lectures, 1966 April-May
    - Chemistry of Molecular Nitrogen by George W Parshall
  - video reel: unidentified (Box 169)
  - audio cassettes (Box 170)
    - unidentified
    - Cleveland lecture, October 1973, with handwritten transcription/notes, 1973 October
    - Lecture, 1972 March 9
    - San Francisco lecture six, 1972 February 10
  - audio reel (Box 170)
    - Rockefeller University talk, 1967 May
    - Columbia talk, 1962 October
    - Caspary talk, 1971 April 6
  - audio spool: unidentified (Box 170)
  - film reel: Biosynthesis of Gramicidan S. by Fritz Lipmann (Box 170)